<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<book>
    <chapter number="95">
        <title>CHAPTER 95</title>

        <p>
            Langdon's eyes had not left the computer screen since the search began.
        </p>

        <p>
            Five minutes. Only two hits. Both irrelevant.
        </p>

        <p>
            He was starting to get worried.
        </p>

        <p>
            Pamela Gettum was in the adjoining room, preparing hot drinks. Langdon and Sophie had inquired
            unwisely if there might be some coffee brewing alongside the tea Gettum had offered, and from the
            sound of the microwave beeps in the next room, Langdon suspected their request was about to be
            rewarded with instant Nescafe.
        </p>

        <p>
            Finally, the computer pinged happily.
        </p>

        <p>
            "Sounds like you got another. What's the title?"
        </p>

        <p>
            Langdon eyed the screen.
        </p>

        <p>
            Grail Allegory in Medieval Literature: A Treatise on Sir Gawain and the Green Knight.
        </p>

        <p>
            "Allegory of the Green Knight."
        </p>

        <p>
            "No good. Not many mythological green giants buried in London."
        </p>

        <p>
            Langdon and Sophie sat patiently in front of the screen and waited through two more dubious
            returns. When the computer pinged again, though, the offering was unexpected.
        </p>

        <p>
            DIE OPERN VON RICHARD WAGNER
        </p>

        <p>
            "The operas of Wagner?"
        </p>

        <p>
            "That seems like a strange match. Was Wagner a knight?"
        </p>

        <p>
            "No. But he was a well-known Freemason. Along with Mozart, Beethoven, Shakespeare,
            Gershwin, Houdini, and Disney. Volumes had been written about the ties between the
            Masons and the Knights Templar, the Priory of Sion, and the Holy Grail. I want to
            look at this one. How do I see the full text?"
        </p>

    </chapter>
</book>